Holds you... like a gold diggin' woman!
Vice Squad is a crime film directed by Arnold Laven.
A Los Angeles police captain (Edward G.
Robinson) ties the case of a slain policeman to a bank robbery, all in a day.
Capt. 'Barnie' Barnaby, played by Edward G. Robinson.
Mona Ross, played by Paulette Goddard.
Ginny, played by K.T. Stevens.
Jack Hartrampf, played by Porter Hall.
Marty Kusalich, played by Adam Williams.
Al Barkis, played by Edward Binns.
Vice Squad is a 1953 American film noir crime film
directed by Arnold Laven and starring Edward G.
Robinson and Paulette Goddard.
The film is also known as The Girl in Room 17.
The film explores themes of cop-killer, bank robbery, vice squad, police drama.